Ross kissed me.
罗斯亲了我
Oh,my God! Oh,my God! Oh,my God!
天啊…
It was unbelievable!
很不可思议吧
Oh,my God! Oh,my God! Oh,my God!
天啊…
Let's hear everything.
现在全部从实招来
Monica,get the wine and unplug the phone.
摩妮卡，拔掉电话线拿酒来
Rachel,does this end well or do we need to get tissues?
瑞秋，结局好不好？ 我们需不需要面纸？
It ended very well.
结局非常好
Do not start without me! Do not start without me!
等我来再讲…
Okay. All right. Let's hear about the kiss.
先谈谈那个吻
Was it a soft brush against your lips...
是像轻拂过你嘴唇的轻吻呢…
...or was it a "I gotta have you now" kind of thing?
还是像… “我现在就要你”的那种吻呢
Well,at first it was really intense, you know? And then....
刚开始很热烈，然后…
Oh,God. And then we just sort of sunk into it.
天啊，然后我们就完全沉醉了
So was he holding you? Or were his hands on your back?
他抱着你吗？ 还是说他的手在你的背上呢？
No,actually,first they started out on my waist...
不，他的手开始时在我腰上
...and then they slid up and were in my hair.
然后往上滑，最后落在我头发上
And...
然后…
...then I kissed her.
…然后我吻了她
Tongue?
舌头？
-Yeah. -Cool.
对 酷
The One With the List
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第08集 清单
All right,check out this bad boy!
各位，瞧瞧这个坏小子
Twelve megabytes of RAM, 500-megabyte hard drive...
12MGRAM 500MG的硬碟…
... built-in spreadsheet capabilities...
里面还有内建试算表的功能…
...and a modem that transmits at over 28,000 BPS.
再加上传输速度 超过两万八BPS的数据机
What will you use it for?
你要用它来嘛啊？
Games and stuff.
玩游戏之类的
There are no jobs. There are no jobs for me.
根本没有工作 没有适合我的工作
Oh,wait,here's one.
等一下，这边有一个
-Would you be willing to cook naked? -There's an ad for a naked chef?
你愿意裸体做菜吗？ 有徵裸体厨师的广告？
No,but if you'll cook naked,then you might be willing to dance naked.
没有，但你如果愿意裸体做菜 你或许会愿意裸体跳舞
And then....
然后…
So how'd you make out last night?
对了，昨晚亲得怎么样了？
That is funny. That is painfully funny.
那真风趣，风趣得很痛苦
No,wait,wait.
不，等等…
Yeah,that's just painful.
对，只是痛苦而已
Wait a minute. I thought last night was great.
我以为昨天晚上很棒耶
Yeah,it was. But I get home...
没错，是很棒 但是当我回到家…
...and I see Julie's saline solution on my night table...
我看到茱莉的食盐水 放在我床边的桌上…
...and I think, "My God! What am I doing?"
我就想“老天啊 我到底在做什么呀？”
Here I am with Julie, this incredible,great woman...
我跟茱莉这么好的女人 在一起…
...who I care about and who cares about me...
…彼此关怀珍惜…
...and I'm just throwing all that away?
而我就那样抛弃一切吗？
You got all that from saline solution?
一瓶食盐水可以讲那么多？
Wait. We're talking about Rachel. You and Rachel.
我们现在是在谈瑞秋 你跟瑞秋
I've been dreaming about me and Rachel for 10 years.
我梦想我跟瑞秋一起 想了十年了
But now I'm with Julie.
但现在我跟茱莉在一起
So it's like,me and Julie, me and Rachel.
就好像我跟茱莉，我跟瑞秋
Me and Julie,me and Rach
我跟茱莉，我跟瑞秋…
Rachel! Rachel.
瑞秋？瑞秋
-Hey,you. -How are you?
你 你好吗？
Good. How are you?
很好，你呢？
Good.
很好
-Hi,honey. -Hi,Julie. Hi,Julie?
亲爱的 茱莉，你好
Julie!
茱莉…
How are you?
你好吗？
Good.
很好
So everybody's here.
大家都在
Everybody's good.
大家都很好
Were you gonna play something?
你不是要弹什么吗，菲比？
-Well,actually -Play it!
其实我没有… 弹啊
All right.
好
-Julie,I didn't know you wore lenses. -What?
我不知道你戴隐形眼镜 什么？
Okay. Hi.
好，嗨
Hello. Hi. Okay.
哈罗，好，嗨
This is a song about a love triangle...
所以，这是一首关于一个…
... between three people I made up.
…我乱编的三角恋爱故事的歌
It's called "Two of Them Kissed Last Night."
叫做“昨晚两个接吻了”
There was a girl We'll call her Betty
有个女孩，我们叫她贝蒂
And a guy Let's call him Neil
有个男孩，咱们叫他尼尔
Now I can't stress This point too strongly
我再三强调这一点
This story isn't real
这故事不是真的
Now our Neil must decide Who will be the girl that he casts aside
现在尼尔必须决定 他要放弃哪一个
Will Betty be the one Who he loves truly
是那个他真心相爱的贝蒂
Or will it be the one Who we'll call Loolie
还是我们称为露莉的女孩
He must decide He must decide
他必须决定，他必须决定
Even though I made him up He must decide
虽然他纯属虚构，他必须决定
Well,this is a nice resume.
你的资历很不错
Nice,nice,nice.
不错…
Muy impressivo.
可以说非常的可观
Mr. Rastatter,what does this job entail? The ad wasn't clear.
这份工作到底是什么呢？ 广告写得很含糊
Macholate.
麻克力
-I'm sorry? -Macholate.
什么？ 麻克力
It's a synthetic chocolate substitute.
一种完全人工的巧克力替代品
Go ahead,try a piece.
别客气，试一块
We think Macholate is even better than chocolate.
对，我们认为 麻克力比巧克力好吃的多了
All right.
好
I love how it crumbles.
我爱这碎碎的感觉
-You see,chocolate doesn't do that. -No,ma'am.
巧克力不会这样 不会
We should be getting our FDA approval any day now.
反正呢，这个食品药物管理局 应该很快就会通过检验了
Hopefully,in time for Thanksgiving.
希望能够赶得上感恩节
The way we see it, chocolate dominates...
照我们看来呢 巧克力已经…
...your major food-preparation holidays. Easter,Christmas,what have you.
…霸占了大部份跟大餐有关的 节日，复活节，圣诞节等
But given the right marketing...
我们在想，只要行销搞好了…
...we can make Thanksgiving the Macholate holiday.
…我们能让感恩节 成为麻克力节
Wow.
哇
Aren't you gonna swallow that?
你不吞下去吗？
Just waiting for it to stop bubbling.
我只是在等泡泡停止
Isn't that great?
是不是很棒？
Well,anyhow...
我们…
...we're looking for chefs who can create Thanksgiving recipes.
…在找几个厨师 来搞一些新感恩节食谱
You interested?
这下你有兴趣吗？
Abso-...
绝对…
... -lutely!
…有
I love creating recipes, I love Thanksgiving,and now...
我爱创新食谱我爱感恩节 而现在呢…
... I love Macholate.
…我爱麻克力
Really?
真的？
Especially that aftertaste. I tell you...
特别是那种口里的余味…
...that'll last you till Christmas.
…可以缭绕到圣诞节
How about Macholate mousse?
麻克力慕斯怎么样？
It's not...
没什么…
...very Thanksgiving-y.
…感恩节的味道
How about Pilgrim Macholate mousse?
那感恩节善信慕斯呢？
What makes it Pilgrim?
哪里像善信啊？
We'll put buckles on it.
放个大铁上去啊
Did Ross call?
罗斯来电话没？
No,I'm sorry.
没有，抱歉
Why didn't he call?
他为什么不打来呢？
He's gonna stay with Julie.
他要跟茱莉在一起是不是？
He's gonna stay with her and she'll be:
他要跟她在一起 然后她会一副：
"Hi,I'm Julie. Ross picked me.
“我是茱莉，罗斯选我”
We'll get married and have lots of kids and dig up stuff together!"
“我们要结婚，生一堆孩子” “然后全家一起去挖骨头”
No offense,but that sounds nothing like her.
恕我冒犯，她不会这样讲的
What am I gonna do? This is like a complete nightmare!
我不知道该怎么办 这简直是一场恶梦
I know. This must be so hard. "Oh,no! Two women love me!
我知道，这一定很难受 “不，两个女人都爱我”
They're both gorgeous, my wallet's too small for my 50s...
两个都是旷世尤物 我的钱太多，皮包装不下…
...and my diamond shoes are too tight!"
…我的钻石鞋太紧了
-Here's a thought -Don't ever touch the computer.
我有一个办法，罗斯 别碰我的电脑，永远都别碰
Ross,listen. I got two words for you:
罗斯，听着 我送你三个字：
Threesome.
三人行
Let's get logical about this. We'll make a list.
我们用理性来分析，好吗？ 我们来列个单子
"Rachel and Julie: Pros and Cons."
“瑞秋和茱莉，优缺点”
We'll put their names in different fonts...
名字用不同字型的粗体字
...and I can use different colors for each column.
然后每一栏 可以用不同的颜色来写上
Can't we use a pen?
不能够用笔就好了吗？
No,Amish boy.
不可以，原始人
Let's start with the cons because they're more fun.
我们就先从缺点开始 那比较好玩一点
Rachel first.
先列瑞秋
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean....
我是说…
All right,I guess you can say she's a little spoiled sometimes.
好吧，我想你可以说她 有时候有一点娇纵
You could say that.
可以这么说
I guess,sometimes she's a little ditzy,you know?
有时候…她有点像傻大姐
And I've seen her be a little too into her looks.
我觉得她有点太注重她的外表
And Julie and I have a lot in common...
茱莉跟我们有很多共同点…
... because we're both paleontologists,right?
…因为我们都是古生物学家
But Rachel's just a waitress.
但是瑞秋她只是个女侍
Waitress.
女侍
Got it. You guys want to play Doom?
好了 你们要玩“毁灭”吗？
Or we could keep doing this.
我们也可以继续
What else?
还有呢？
I don't know.
我不知道
Oh! Her ankles are a little chubby.
她的脚踝有一点胖
Okay,let's do Julie.
换茱莉了
What's wrong with her?
她有什么不好的？
She's not Rachel.
她不是瑞秋
This is pumpkin pie with a Macholate crust.
这是麻克力饼屑南瓜馅饼
This is Macholate cranberry cake, and these are Macholate-chip cookies.
这个是麻克力红莓蛋糕 而这些是麻克力饼干
Just like the lndians served.
跟印第安人的一样
Oh,my God!
天啊
"Oh,my God" good?
“天啊”很好？
Oh,my God! I can't believe you let me put this in my mouth.
天啊 我不敢相信你给我吃这个
Sweet Lord! This is what evil must taste like!
这一定是万恶之味
I tell you,it won't print.
我说这个玩意儿不能印
I pressed that button,like,100 times.
对，那个按钮我按了一百次了
For a hotline,you're not so hot.
对热线而言，你没有那么热
What is that in the background?
什么？我听到了什么？
Are you watching Star Trek?
你在看“星舰迷航记”？
So did you break Julie's heart?
你让茱莉心碎了吗？
It was horrible. She cried,I cried. She threw things,they hit me.
是啊，好可怕，她哭，我也哭 她丢东西，打到了我
I did the right thing.
我这么做是对的
So Spock actually hugs his father?
史巴克真的拥抱了他爸爸吗？
Hey,do you guys have
你们有没…
Where you going?
你去哪儿了？
I just got back...
我刚刚…
...from Julie's.
…从茱莉那边回来
No,no.
不…
It's not what you think.
不是你想的那样
It's the other thing.
是别的事
Well,what's the other thing? What do I think?
什么是别的事？
Well....
这个嘛…
He broke up with Julie!
他跟茱莉分手了
Well,go hug her,for God's sakes!
老天在上，去抱抱她呀
Really?
真的？
Really.
真的
It's always been you,Rach.
我爱的一直是你
Oh,God.
天啊
Oh,this is good.
这真好
-This is really good. -I know. I know.
这真的很好 我知道…
It's almost....
几乎…
What do you say we take a walk? Just us. Not them.
我们出去走一走怎么样？ 就我们两个人
-Let me get my coat. -Okay. No,hey!
好，我去拿外套 好，不…
I'll get your coat.
我帮你拿
He's going to get my coat. He's going to get my coat,Joey!
他去帮我拿外套 他去帮我拿外套，乔伊
Joey,I can't believe this! This is unbelievable!
我真不敢相信
-What's that? -What? Nothing!
那是什么？ 什么？没什么
-I saw my name. What is it? -No,no,see? See?
我看到我的名字，是什么？ 不，不，你看…
It's printing!
在印了
Let me see!
那是什么嘛？给我看
Hey,someone order a coat?
有人订外套吗？
Chandler wrote something about me and won't let me see.
罗斯，钱德在电脑上 写了关于我的事还不让我看
He won't? He won't!
他不…
Because isn't that...
因为那是不是…
...the short story you were writing?
你正在写的短篇故事
Yes,it is a short story...
对，那是一篇我正在写的…
...that I was writing.
…短篇故事
And I'm in it? Let me read it.
里面有我？ 那让我看啊
No!
不…
-Come on! -Hey,why don't you read it to her?
好啦 干脆你念给她听好了
All right.
好吧
"It was summer.
那个时候是夏天
And it was hot.
天气很热
Rachel was there.
瑞秋在那里…
A lonely gray couch.
寂寞的灰沙发
'Oh,look!' cried Ned.
奈德大叫“看啊”
And the kingdom was his forever. The end!"
然后他就是永远的国王了 剧终
That's all you wrote? You're the worst writer in the world!
就这样？你只写了这样？ 你是全世界最烂的作家
This isn't funny anymore.
好了，我不再觉得好玩了
There's something about me on that paper,and I want to see it.
那张纸上写了关于我的事情 而我想要看一看
No,you don't.
不，不可以
All right,fine. If you guys want to be children,that's fine.
好吧，你们要这么孩子气的话 没关系
I do not need to see it!
我根本就不需要看
What is this?
这是什么？
That is....
这是…
What is this?
罗斯，这是什么？
-Thank you. -Good luck.
谢谢 祝你好运
Okay. Just remember how crazy I am about you,okay?
你只要记得我多为你疯狂
"Kind of ditzy"?
“有点傻大姐”？
"Too into her looks"?
“太注重外表”？
"Spoiled"?
“娇纵”？
A little spoiled. He was supposed to type "little," the idiot!
是有一点娇纵 他应该加上“有一点”才对
"Just a waitress"?
“只是个女侍？”
Now that was....
那是…
I mean,as opposed to....
我是说，相对于…
Okay,is this over yet? Rach?
你念完了没有，瑞秋？
I do not have chubby ankles!
我的脚踝一点都不肥
No! I
不，瑞秋…
Okay,look at the other side. Look at Julie's column.
好…你看另一边嘛 你看看茱莉那一栏
"She's not Rachem"?
“她不是瑞琪”？
What the hell's a Rachem?
瑞琪是什么东西啊
Is that a stupid paleontology word...
那是什么？因为我是女侍…
... I wouldn't know, because I'm just a waitress?
而不懂得愚蠢古生物用语吗？
Rach,come on!
不，瑞秋，你不要这样
It's "She's not Rachel"!
是“她不是瑞秋”
She's not....
她不是…
My diary! Brilliant!
我的日记太聪明了
If I'd said it was my diary, she wouldn't have made me read it.
我应该说那是我的日记 她绝对不会逼我念我的日记
That's true. You'd be a great person to have around after an emergency.
那倒是真的，你很适合在 紧急事件的第二天放马后炮
I cannot believe Ross even made this list.
真不敢相信罗斯列了单子
-I know. -What a dinkus!
我知道 简直浑蛋
Hey,cut him some slack. It was Chandler's idea.
放他一马吧 那是钱德的主意
What?
什么？
Oh,good. I was hoping that would come up.
很好，我正在希望你提呢
This was your idea?
这是你的主意？
Let's get some perspective here. These things happen for a reason.
拜托，你们想一下 事出必有因
Yeah. You!
对，是你呀
Pheebs,back me up. You believe in that karma crap,don't you?
菲菲，帮我一下，好吗？ 你相信宿命那套狗屁，对吧？
By the way,good luck in your next life as a dung beetle.
对，祝你下辈子当大便虫好运
Rach!
瑞秋
Hey! Open up! Please?
瑞秋，瑞秋，开门
When somebody does not buzz you in, Ross,that means,"Go away."
当别人不开门让你进来的时候 那表示“走开”
It doesn't mean, "Climb up the fire escape."
那并不表示请你爬防火梯上来
I just want to read you your "Pro List."
我只是想念一点 你的优点给你听
Not interested.
我不感兴趣
"Number one: the way you cry at game shows.
第一，你看游戏节目时会哭
Number two: how much you love your friends.
第二，你对你朋友的感情
Number three: the way you play with your hair when you're nervous.
第三，你紧张的时候 玩你头发的样子
Number four: how brave you are for starting your life over.
第四，勇敢地开始你的新生活
Number five: how great you are with Ben.
第五，你很会逗小班
Number six: the way you smell."
第六，还有你的香味
What are you doing?
罗斯，你在干什么？
You want to open the window?
乔伊，帮我开窗，好不好？
Oh,yeah.
好呀，来
-What are you doing out there? -I'm....
你在外面干什么？ 我…我…
You must be freezing. You know what you need?
天啊，你一定冷死了 知道你需要什么吗？
How about a nice,steaming cup of hot Macholate?
来杯热腾腾的麻克力怎么样？
Come on,open up.
阿秋，开门
Rach,come on. You gotta give me another chance.
阿秋，别这样嘛 你再给我一次机会
No.
不
-No? -That's what I said.
不？ 不就是不
Maybe we should go.
也许我们该离开一下
You don't have to go. We're done.
不，你们真的不用走 我们已经谈完了
I know how you must
拜托，我知道你一定…
No! You don't,Ross.
不，你不，罗斯
Imagine the worst things you think about yourself.
想像一下 你觉得自己最糟的地方
How would you feel if the person you trusted most in the world...
如果这个世界上 你最信任的人…
... not only thinks them too...
不只也这样想
... but actually uses them as reasons not to be with you.
而且用来当做不跟你在一起的 理由，换了你会怎么样？
No,but see,I want to be with you in spite of all those things.
就算是那样 我还是想要跟你在一起
Well,that's mighty big of you.
你真是宽宏大量，罗斯
I said,don't go!
我说，别走
You know what?
你知道吗？
If it were the other way around,there is nothing you could put on a list...
如果今天是你列单子…
...that would make me not want to be with you.
…不管你在单子上头写些什么 都阻止不了我跟你在一起
Well,then I guess that's the difference between us.
我猜我们就是那一点不同
See,I'd never make a list.
我绝对不会去列单子
I never know how long to wait in this situation before you can talk.
每一次遇上这种情况 我都不知道要等多久才能开口
Maybe a little longer.
我再等一会儿好了
In these recipes, the quantities may seem unusual.
我其中的一些食谱用的 麻克力份量或许有点不寻常
Like these coconut Macholate holiday nut bars?
像这个椰子麻克力干果棒
I've indicated four cups of coconut and four cups of nuts...
我上面写了四杯椰子 四杯碎干果…
...and only one tablespoon of Macholate.
…而只有一大匙的麻克力
Doesn't matter.
没关系
Our FDA approval didn't come through.
食品药物管理局没有通过
Something about laboratory rats.
实验室老鼠出了问题
Gosh,I'm sorry.
天啊，真遗撼…
Yeah.
是呀
Anyhow,here's your check.
反正，这是给你的支票
Thank you for all the trouble you went through.
还有谢谢你出了这么多力
Listen,you didn't eat a lot of it while you were cooking,did you?
你做的时候没有吃很多吧？
Well,I ate some.
我吃了一些
Oh,some is fine. Some is not a lot.
一些，那还好 一些可以，一些不是很多
So it doesn't burn when you pee,does it?
那你尿尿的时候 没有灼痛的感觉吧？
Is that him again?
又是他吗？
Tell him I'd come to the phone, but my ankles are weighing me down.
告诉他我很想去接 可是我脚踝太粗走不动
I don't think this is the best time.
我想现在时机不对
Look,can you do something for me?
你帮我一个忙，好不好？
Sure. What?
当然，什么事？
All right.
好的
Music?
音乐？
Sure.
没问题
The next one's dedicated to Rachel from Ross.
下一首是 罗斯要点给瑞秋的歌曲
Rachel,he wants you to know he's sorry for what he did...
瑞秋，他要你知道 他为他的行为深感抱歉
...and he hopes you can forgive him.
…希望你能从心里原谅他
See the stones set in your eyes
看到你眼若冰霜
See the thorn twist in your side
看到你浑身带刺
I'll wait for you
我会等你的
Sleight of hand and twist of fate
上天实在作弄人
On a bed of nails she makes me wait
她就让我苦苦的等
And I'll wait without you
不论你是否在身旁，我会等的
We've just gotten a call from Rachel and she told us what Ross did.
我们刚接到瑞秋的电话 她告诉我们罗斯做了什么
It's pretty appalling. And,Ross,if you're listening...
真令人发指 罗斯，如果你在听…
...I don't want to play your song anymore.
…我不想再放你点的歌了
Why don't we devote our time to a couple that stands a chance?
我们何不将时间 留给还有机会的情侣
Avery,Michelle's sorry she hit you with her car...
艾佛 米雪很抱歉用她的车撞你
...and she hopes you two will work it out.
她希望你们能够解决问题
There's a room where
我有个房间…
I can go
…可以去
And tell my secrets to
倾吐心中的秘密
In my room
在我房里
Thanks for coming in again.
谢谢你再度光临
Not at all. I have no morals, and I need the cash.
不客气 我既无道德又需要钱
It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
我们真是一丘之貉
Anyway,they're called Fish-tachios.
这个东西叫做开心鱼
They taste exactly like pistachios...
吃起来是跟开心果一样的…
... but they're made of reconstituted fish bits.
但主要是用鱼肉重新压制的…
Here,try one.
来，试试看
-All right. -You're not allergic to anything?
好吧 你没有什么过敏问题吧？
Cat hair.
猫毛
Oh,sorry.
抱歉